UNITE Photographs 6000 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Photographs
1926-2005
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE-HERE
6000 P
25.06 cubic feet
25.1 linear ft.
Photographs.
7705075
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, May 15, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 30, 2015
Biographical / Historical
UNITE, the Union of Needle Trades, Industrial, and Textile Employees was formed in 1995 after a merger between the International Ladies' Garment Workers Union (ILGWU) and the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU).
In 2004 they announced they would merge with the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE) which created UNITE HERE.
Jay Mazur served as president of UNITE from its beginning until his retirement in 2001. Bruce Raynor was elected president at that time and served until the HERE merger.
Scope and Contents
This collection has over 12,000 photographs, 400 slides and several CD's of photographs documenting the history of UNITE.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6000/016 P: UNITE Local 169 Amalgamated Northeast Regional Joint Board Photographs 6000/018 P: UNITE Pacific Northwest District Council Photographs 6000/024 P: UNITE Local 23-25 Photographs 6000/033 P: UNITE Local 155 Photographs 6000/037 P: UNITE Communications Department Photographs 6000/043 P: UNITE Editor Photographs 6000/044 P: UNITE Photographs 6000/049 P: UNITE Local 9 Photographs 6000/050 P: UNITE Local 10 and Local 23-25 Photographs
Textile industry -- New York (State) -- New York; Textile workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York; Sweatshops -- New York (State) -- New York; Clothing trade -- New York (State) -- New York; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union; Textile Workers Union of America; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; UNITE HERE (Organization)
7705075
- Broadsides - You're naked without it (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  2 copies
- Broadsides - Get dressed. (And make the world a better place.) (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Broadsides - One size fits all. (Box 2, Folder 3)
- UNITE! (Box 3, Folder 1)
  items were removed from box 1 and box was deleted, not enough content to warrant taking up shelf space, so contents were consolidated in this box---- 2 photographs; 1 floppy disc
- Summer 2003 Rejects (Box 3, Folder 2)
  27 photographs; 2 slides
- Summer 2002 Rejects (Box 3, Folder 3)
  224 photographs
- Summer 2002 Rejects (Box 3, Folder 4)
  43 slides; 95 photographs
- Assorted used and original cartoons (Box 3, Folder 5)
  1 photograph
- UNITE Fall 2002 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  29 photographs; 14 slides
- Fall 2002 - Pictures and Rejects (Box 3, Folder 7)
  34 photographs
- UNITE Magazine/Spring 2003 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  24 photographs; 1 slide
- UNITE Magazine - Summer 2003, Vol. 9, no.2 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  10 photographs; 1 slide
- 8/3/1999 - Unidentified Shop (Box 3, Folder 10)
  18 photographs
- Local 169 - Election Day -- 11/7/2000 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Bruce Raynor/Mary O'Brien - ILDC Merger, New Jersey (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Bergen County CLC - Phil McLewan - 10/15/1998 -- Patrick Byrne, UNITE Pres. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  14 photographs
- Columbus Coated Fabrics UNITE - 5/7/1998 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  84 photographs
- UNITE w/Congress -- Eva Clayton (Box 3, Folder 15)
  27 photographs
- Locker Action - UNITE -- 3/25/1999 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  8 photographs
- UNITE - Jay Mazur - Local 23-25, 8/28/1998 -- Chinatown Demo (Box 3, Folder 17)
  16 photographs
- UNITE - Kennson Binder, Ontario by Jonathan Eaton (Box 3, Folder 18)
  7 photographs
- UNITE -- 2/21/1999 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Local 1871 - Central Labor Co. (Box 3, Folder 20)
  5 photographs
- UNITE - Chicago Lauderies - 1st Contract (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Jayo Sportswear, Bethlehem, PA 1998 - Maria Stephens (Box 3, Folder 22)
  9 photographs
- Capitol Times - Madison, WI -- Hank Koshollek (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Donna Karan, NYC; Barbara Streisand, Wedding Gown (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Fall 2001 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  11 photographs
- Winter 2001 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  22 photographs
- Spring 2002 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Summer 2002 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  20 photographs
- Fall scans 2001 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  66 photographs; 39 slides
- Winter 2002 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  8 photographs, 1 slide
- Fall 2002 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  3 slides12 photographs
- Spring 2003 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Fall 2001 Issue (Box 3, Folder 33)
  14 photographs; 23 slides
- Fall 2001 Issue (Box 3, Folder 34)
  1 floppy; 22 photographs
- Fall 2001 Issue (Box 3, Folder 35)
  The Garment Center: Still in Fashion
- FTAA Protest - Ohio - Workers Memorial Day 4/28 - Summer 2001 Issue (Box 4, Folder 1)
  144 photographs
- FTAA Rally - Quebec City - April 21, 2001 -- Rejects (Box 4, Folder 2)
  4 photographs
- Summer 2001 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  13 photographs; 34 slides
- Summer 2001 Issue (Box 4, Folder 4)
  23 photographs; 1 slide
- Summer 2001 Issue (Box 4, Folder 5)
  2 slides; 39 photographs
- Summer 2001 Rejects (Box 4, Folder 6)
  24 photographs
- Summer 2000 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  50 photographs; 13 slides
- 2000 Election Picnic (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Winter 2000 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  33 photographs; 15 slides
- Shops - Bemis Bags (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Winter 2000 Issue - Used and rejected (Box 4, Folder 11)
  10 slides; 49 photographs
- Fall/Winter 1999 Issue (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Fall-Winter 1999 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  71 photographs; 14 slides
- Summer 1999 Issue (Box 4, Folder 14)
  33 photographs
- Summer 1999 Issue (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Cover Summer 2000 - Internet (Box 4, Folder 16)
  156 slides
- Pushing Carts - Cynthia Steffe (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Ceramic Shop (Box 4, Folder 18)
  3 photographs
- Aramark Uniform - Chicago Press Cong. 3/19/1999 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Unidentified Negatives (Box 4, Folder 20)
- UNITE - K-mart Rally (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Election Rally UNITE -- 2/1999 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Amdov Diello Rally (Box 4, Folder 23)
- UNITE Canada -- French pages (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Local 10 Cutters - Dalma Dress/NYC (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Garment Workers (Box 4, Folder 26)
  6 photographs
- Shop Stewards (Box 4, Folder 27)
  12 photographs
- Short takes (Box 4, Folder 28)
  13 photographs; 2 slides
- Solidarity (Box 5, Folder 1)
  15 photographs
- Winter 1999 - Spanish Edition (Box 5, Folder 2)
- July/Aug 1998 - Spanish Edition (Box 5, Folder 3)
  2 photographs
- May/June 1998 COPE-Spanish (Box 5, Folder 4)
- May/June 1998 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  1 slide
- March/April 1998 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- March /April 1997 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Jan/Feb 1998 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Nov/Dec 1997 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Nov/Dec 1997 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- July/Aug 1997 - Spanish COPE School (Box 5, Folder 11)
- July/Aug 1997 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  19 photographs; 1 slide
- May/June 1997 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  3 photographs; 2 slide
- Nov/Dec 1996 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Sept/Oct 1996 - Spanish Edition (Box 5, Folder 15)
- July/Aug 1996 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  Newsclippings; 9 photographs
- N. Jersey Region (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Northeast, W. PA and Ohio Dept. (Box 5, Folder 18)
  8 photographs; 2 slides
- Pacific North West District Council (Box 5, Folder 19)
- PA, OH, S. Jersey Joint Board (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Southern Regional Joint Board (Box 5, Folder 21)
  66 photographs; 1 slide
- Southwest Region (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Western Regional Joint Board (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Western States (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Cartoons (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Children/Kids (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Child labor (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Chinese Supp-- (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Civil Rights (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Contracts (Box 5, Folder 30)
  52 photographs
- Convention (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Education (Box 5, Folder 32)
  40 photographs
- ESL (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Skills training (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Trade/NAFTA (Box 5, Folder 35)
- WARNACO (Box 5, Folder 36)
- General Office (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Graphic Images (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Health and Safety (Box 5, Folder 39)
  29 photographs
- Health (Box 5, Folder 40)
  4 photographs; 1 slide
- Health Issues (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Sidney Hillman (Box 5, Folder 42)
- History (Box 5, Folder 43)
  7 photographs; 1 slide
- Hobbies (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Immigration (Box 5, Folder 45)
- International (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Justice Center (Box 5, Folder 47)
  2 photographs; 2 slides
- Labor Day (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Legislative (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Media Matter (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Obituaries (Box 5, Folder 51)
- Organizing (Box 5, Folder 52)
  59 photographs
- UNITE (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Student Activity (Box 5, Folder 54)
- Sweatshops (Box 5, Folder 55)
  56 photographs
- AMTEX (Box 5, Folder 56)
- A. Philip Randolph (Box 5, Folder 57)
- Art (Box 5, Folder 58)
- Babies and Banners (Box 5, Folder 59)
- Bachrach (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Banners (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Barneys (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Barneys 1993 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Beasley, Noel (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Bedden, Gussie (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Belton (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Bernstein and Sons (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Biddeford Textile (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Botto House (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Bradley Scott (Box 6, Folder 11)
  10 photographs
- Bennett, Ernest (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Brazilian Trade Union Leaders (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Webster Brick (Orange, VA) (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Bright of America (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Brown, Clayola (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Burma-Bibas (Tie Factory) (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Canada (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Canon Organizing - 1986 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Chair (Ergonomic) (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Chicago/Central States Jt. Bd. (Spotlight Story) (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Clark, Ed (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Cleveland Joint Board (Spotlight Story) (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Clinton, Bill (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Clothing Industry (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Clothing ratification (Universal Clothing, New York) 1980 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Clothing Strike 1974 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Cooper Sportswear (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Cotton Dust (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Cotton Dust Demonstration 5/19/1981 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  42 photographs; news clippings
- Crystal Springs, Mississippi (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Seminoll Company (Box 7, Folder 1)
  24 phot0graphs
- Service and Allied Industries Joint Board (Spotlight Story) (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Sheinkman, Jack (Box 7, Folder 3)
  88 photographs
- Sheinkman, Jack (Box 7, Folder 4)
  32 photographs
- Shirtmakers (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Shoe Div. - Heel Turners of Haverhill Story - Local 12 A (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Shoe Div. - Last Makers (Story) -- The Last Comes First (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Shoe Div. - Common Problems, Common Goals (Story) (Box 7, Folder 8)
  13 photographs
- Shoe Div. - Ballet Shoes - Selva Mfg. Co. (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Shoe Workers - Sobel, Bernstein and Greene Shoe Factory (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Social Services (Box 7, Folder 11)
  36 photographs
- Solidarity Day - 1991 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- South Africa (Box 7, Folder 13)
  71 photographs
- Southern Region Merger Conf. 1990 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Stearns, Kentucky (Box 7, Folder 15)
  20 photographs; 10 slides
- Takata (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Tenn. Woolens (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Local 23-25 (Old) (Box 8, Folder 1)
  41 photographs
- 3/1987 GEB (Box 8, Folder 2)
- David Melman (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Mazur, Jay (Box 8, Folder 4)
  37 photographs
- Anti-Apartheid (Box 8, Folder 5)
- PACE - Sae Gae Times, Cho Sun Daily News, etc. (Box 8, Folder 6)
- La Mode (Box 8, Folder 7)
- El Paso, Photographer-Jim Tynan / Summer 1991 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- UMWA Strike (Box 8, Folder 9)
  72 photographs
- Poverty-Welfare Mother; Mother Hale House (Box 8, Folder 10)
- PAI Photos -- Plant Closings; Unemployment line (Box 8, Folder 11)
- La Miscellaneous Shots (Box 8, Folder 12)
  70 photographs
- ILGWU Convention 1992 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Convention Photos - unused -- developed by Joe Miller (Box 8, Folder 14)
  62 photographs
- Convention photos - unused -- developed by Joe Miller (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Labor Day 1990 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  17 photographs
- Labor Day 1992 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- 1986 Convention Pictures - Used (Box 8, Folder 20)
  47 photographs
- 1986 Homework Hearings (Box 8, Folder 21)
- American Family Day Celebration -- May, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  22 photographs; 23 slides
- Pro-Choice March -- April 9, 1989 -- Washington, DC (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Personalities and Pols./ACTWU (Box 8, Folder 24)
  19 photographs
- ILGWU Penn Station South (Box 8, Folder 25)
  25 photographs
- History/ACTWU (Box 8, Folder 26)
  30 photographs; 2 slides
- Covenant House, NYC (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Portraits/ACTWU (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Suzy Curtains/ACTWU -- 8/19/1989 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- History ACTWU/Canada (Box 9, Folder 3)
- People Working/UNITE/ACTWU (Box 9, Folder 4)
- ACTWU Color Shop Pix / Susan Williamson (Box 9, Folder 5)
  9 photographs; 1 slide
- ACTWU/Anti-Apartheid (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Civil Rights/ACTWU (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Education, Registration/ACTWU (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Haiti/ACTWU (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Health and Safety (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Health Center/ACTWU (Box 9, Folder 11)
- UNITE/Demonstrations (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Demos/ACTWU; Strikes and UNITE (Box 9, Folder 13)
  28 photographs
- JP Stevens (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Maquiladoras Tour; ACTWU, Feb. 2005/Picadras Negras, Mexico (Box 9, Folder 15)
- ILGWU and Early UNITE; Clothing/NY (Box 9, Folder 16)
  73 photographs
- Shop Photos - UNITE and ILGWU (Box 9, Folder 17)
- NY - NJ Joint Board (Box 9, Folder 18)
- New England Regional Joint Board (Box 9, Folder 19)
- NY Apparel and Allied Workers Joint Board (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Local 10 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Local 23-25 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Local 62-32 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Local 89-22-1 (Photos) (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Local 99 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Local 155 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Local 340 (Photos) (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Local 438- Vt. (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Chicago and Central States (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Mid-Atlantic Region (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Midwest Regional Joint Board (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Baltimore Regional Joint Board (Box 9, Folder 32)
- New England Region (Box 9, Folder 33)
- We are the ILG (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Miscellaneous Photos (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Miscellaneous Photos (Box 9, Folder 36)
- James Hazuka; Alex and Trish; N. Charleston, S.C. and Charlotte, NC (Box 9, Folder 37)
- UNITE! (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Pictures Montreal Organizing (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Rejects - Winter 2001 (Box 9, Folder 40)
- Personalities (Box 9, Folder 41)
- Politics - COPE School (Box 9, Folder 42)
  2 photograph
- Politics (Box 9, Folder 43)
  79 photographs; 1 slide
- July 29, Lobby Day (Box 9, Folder 44)
- President's column (Box 9, Folder 45)
- Promotions (Box 9, Folder 46)
- Retirees (Box 9, Folder 47)
  38 photographs
- Sewing and Tailor/ACTWU (Box 9, Folder 48)
- UNITE - Folks Working (Box 9, Folder 49)
- Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 9, Folder 50)
  67 photographs
- Winter 2001 issue (Box 10, Folder 1)
  Text
- Winter 2001 issue (Box 10, Folder 2)
  22 photographs; 1 slide
- Winter 2001 issue (Box 10, Folder 3)
  35 photographs
- Rejects, Winter 2001 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  21 photographs
- Quebec (Montreal) (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Canada (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Tiercon (filed under Canada); Photos marked as "Canadian Phots from Tullia" (Box 10, Folder 7)
- GS (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 10, Folder 9)
- UNITE! (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Negatives and Contact Sheets (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Protest Photographs (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Personnel photographed at Magee-Reiter in Bloomsburg (Box 10, Folder 13)
  3 photographs; 15 slides
- Portraits (Box 10, Folder 14)
- So.East (Box 10, Folder 15)
  53 photographs
- So.East (Box 10, Folder 16)
  109 photographs
- UNITE! Photographs (Box 10, Folder 17)
  41 photographs; 3 slides
- UNITE Magazine -- Spring 2002, Vol. 8, no. 1 -- Rejects (Box 10, Folder 18)
  54 photographs
- Spring 2002 Rejects (Box 10, Folder 19)
  26 photographs
- UNITE! Magazine - Spring 2002, vol. 8, no.1 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  31 photographs
- Rejects Winter 2001 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Shoes and Hats/ACTWU; Chair Dyers (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Summer 2001 Issue (Box 10, Folder 23)
- NY UNITE Members (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Winter 2002 UNITE! (Box 10, Folder 25)
  52 photographs; 1 slide
- Abortion Rights Demo (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Actor Conference 1992 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Actor-ACCTWU Retirees (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Actor Workshop - Chicago 1994 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Actors Equity (Box 12, Folder 5)
- ACTWU Civil Rights Committee (Box 12, Folder 6)
- ACTWU Logos (Box 12, Folder 7)
- ACTWU - the Magician (Box 12, Folder 8)
- ACTWU - Photos for Campaign Literature (Box 12, Folder 9)
- ACTWU Sign. Times Square 12/1981 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- ACTWU - PAC Award Winners (Box 12, Folder 11)
- ACTWU Pin (Box 12, Folder 12)
- ACTWU - Social Service Conference 12/1987 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- ACTWU Voices - 1989 Anniversary Series - Oral Histories (Box 12, Folder 14)
- ACTWUSA (Box 12, Folder 15)
- ACTWUSA Visit 1988 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- AFL-CIO Natl Convention on Job Safety and Health (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Africans (Box 12, Folder 18)
- After Six Formal Wear (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Aging is definitely a plus (story) (Box 12, Folder 20)
- AIDS inset LU 9/1988 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- AIDS March/July 1992 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- AIDS Walk -- 1999 - NYC (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Allentown, PA (Organizing drive) (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Alleruzzon, John (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Allied Chemical Co. (TAA) (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Allied Signal (Box 12, Folder 27)
- ALNMAX (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Alcoholism (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Joe Alvarez (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Amalgamated Insurance (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Gar Alperovitz (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Amalgamated Bank (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Amalgamated Bank - Ill. (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers Convention (1974) (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Amalgamated Services and Allied Industries Joint Board (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Amal. Service an dAllied Industries Joint Board (Box 12, Folder 37)
- American Cyanamid (Box 12, Folder 38)
- American Fashion Group (Box 12, Folder 39)
- American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA) (Box 12, Folder 40)
- American Flag (Box 12, Folder 41)
- American History (Box 13, Folder 1)
  2
- AMOKO Fabracs (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Anchundia, Piedad (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Andalusia, Alabana (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Anderson, S.C. (organizing) (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Angelica Health Care Services (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Angelica/Canada (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Animal Workers (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Anti-Apartheid Rally - 8/13/1985-6/14/1986 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Apartheid (Box 13, Folder 10)
- AP parts (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Antoniades, Ruth (Box 13, Folder 12)
- April 25th Mobilization (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Arkansas (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Armitrage Shanks, Mooresville, NC (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Armstrong - Canada (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Arnprior, Ontario (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Arrests - Bimbels (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Art Contest - 1988 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Art Contest - 1981 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Art Fillers - (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Art Work (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Arthritis (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Asbestos (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Ashland Shirt (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Atrium (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Audrey Celine, Inc. (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Auto Parts Division (Box 13, Folder 28)
- AVTEX (Box 13, Folder 29)
- Ax, Joel (Box 13, Folder 30)
- Bachrach Portraits Studio (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Back Pay Awards (Box 13, Folder 32)
- Bag and Packaging Conference ( St. Louis, Mo.) (Box 13, Folder 33)
- Baltimore (Box 13, Folder 34)
- Baltimore Day Care Center (Box 13, Folder 35)
- Baltimore Regional Joint Board (Box 13, Folder 36)
- Baltimore Stewards Workshop 1991 (Box 13, Folder 37)
- Barnstable Bus Co. (Hyannis, Mass.) (Box 13, Folder 38)
- BATA Shoe (Box 13, Folder 39)
- Bates Campaign (Box 13, Folder 40)
- Bemis (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Benchmark, Inc. (Barnsville, Miss.) (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Benzidene (Box 14, Folder 3)
  graphics
- Berkshire Hathaway Plant (New Bedford, Mass.) (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Berry Hill Nursing Home; So. Boston, VA; Midatlantic Joint Board (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Bi-County Joint Board (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Bi-County Joint Board, Eden, NC (Spotlight - L.U. 12/1977) (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Black America Story (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Black South African Unionists (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Bladder Cancer (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Blue Bird Fabrics (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Blue Mountain Arts Co. (Organizing) (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Blue Ridge Workers Assoc., Galax, VA. (Box 14, Folder 13)
  1 photographs
- Borders of Exploitation (Undocumented Workers Story) (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Union Label - Boycotts - Picketing - Boss Glove Campaign (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Boston Jobless Conference 1984 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Brilliant, Alabama (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Brooks Brothers (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Brooks Bros./NC (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Freddie Brooks (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Buffalo Joint Board (Textile) --- Story: Labor Union Women move into Leadership (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Builder, Nick (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Buildings (Abandoned) (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Burlington Industries (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Calendar -- 1979 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- California Joint Board (Box 14, Folder 26)
- California Retiree's Club (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Camp 7 Inc. - Longmont, Colorado (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Canada (Box 14, Folder 29)
  87 photographs
- Canada - Adidas (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Canadian Women: problems/Strengths (Story) (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Canada - Harding Carpets/Closing (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Canada-Imports (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Canadian Agreement Story (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Canada Conference/ACTWU -- 5/1991 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Canada Conference - 1988 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- 4th Canadian Conference 1985 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Canadian Conference 1979 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Canadian Conference (1977) (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Canadian Conference 1983 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Canadian Health Insurance (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Canadian Labour Congress 1978 (Convention) (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Canadian Occup/Safety and Health (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Canadian School (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Canselmo, Caroline (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Jimmy Carter (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Cartoons (not imports) (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Catawba (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Cavalier Clothes (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Mike Cavanugh (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Central Mass. Joint Board (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Central-South Jersey Joint Board (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Century Circuits (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Chicago Joint Board (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board (Box 15, Folder 25)
  49 photographs
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board Conference 1992 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Chicago/Central States Joint Board Housing Project for Senior Residences (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Chicago/Central States Joint Board Leadership Training School - Ottawa, Ill. (1982) (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Chicago/Central States Leadership Training School 1981 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Chicago and Central State Joint Board Summer School (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Chicago and Central States - Voter Registration (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Child Care (Box 16, Folder 7)
- China (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Chipman (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Christmas 1989 Cover (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Civil Rights CF 11-12/1993 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Civil Rights Conference 1993 - Alabama (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Clark, Ramsey (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Cleveland Joint Board (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Clothing Anniversary Celeb. (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Clothing Shops (Box 16, Folder 16)